We all want to save money, and with the cost of living on the rise in the UK, it’s become more important than ever to watch what we spend.
我们都想省钱，而随着英国生活成本不断上涨，精打细算变得比以往任何时候都更加重要。
The biggest increase in our expenditure at the moment is on energy – the oil, gas and electricity we use to power and heat our homes.
目前我们开销中增长最明显的部分是能源开支——也就是用于家庭供电和供暖的燃油、燃气以及电费。
That’s why many of us are looking at ways to save energy so we don’t have to shell out on huge fuel bills.
这也是为什么许多人都在寻找节能方法，避免为高昂的能源账单买单。
Making our home more energy efficient is the obvious way to save money.
显而易见，让我们的家更节能是省钱的有效途径。
To try to achieve this, new homes in the UK will be banned from installing new gas and oil boilers by 2025.
为了实现这一目标，英国将从2025年起禁止新建住宅安装燃气和燃油锅炉。
Having a heat pump instead can help save energy, but they’re unaffordable for many people, unless they’ve got spare cash stashed away.
改用热泵有助于节能，但对很多人来说，除非手头有闲钱储蓄，否则热泵的价格实在难以负担。
If your home feels like a money pit, there are some low-budget solutions you can turn to to lower your energy usage.
如果感觉你的家一直在“烧钱”，有一些低成本的方法可以降低能源消耗。
Warm air escapes our homes easily, so adding draught excluders or a rolled-up towel to block these gaps will help.
室内的暖气很容易从缝隙流失，因此安装防风条，或是用卷起来的毛巾堵住这些缝隙，都会有帮助。
Investing in new double glazing will certainly insulate your home better, but if it is too costly, it might be worth using some heavy curtains to stop the heat escaping.
安装新的双层玻璃窗固然能更好地为房屋保温，但如果成本过高，挂厚窗帘来阻止热量散失也是个不错的选择。
Switching off lights is also a good idea.
随手关灯同样是个好习惯。
But there are lots of other little things we can do around the home that will help save energy, don’t cost a fortune and that just require tweaks to our behaviour. They could be as good as installing, fitting or making anything.
不过，我们还可以在家中做很多其他小事来节能，这些方法不仅成本低廉，而且只需要稍微调整一下日常习惯，效果不亚于安装任何节能设备。
Put lids on pots and pans when cooking – the food will be ready quicker. Use a microwave to reheat food rather than the oven. Don’t overfill your kettle when boiling water, and don’t leave electrical items on standby.
做饭时给锅碗瓢盆盖上盖子，食物会熟得更快；用微波炉加热剩菜，而不是用烤箱；烧开水时不要把水壶装得太满；不用电器时别让它们处于待机状态。
Jo Patterson from Cardiff University’s Welsh School of Architecture told the BBC that a combination of small measures like these could reduce household energy bills by about 10%.
卡迪夫大学威尔士建筑学院的乔·帕特森在接受BBC采访时表示，将这些小举措结合起来，大约能为家庭减少10%的能源账单支出。
So, we’re being encouraged to be more fuel efficient.
因此，人们被鼓励提高能源利用效率。
But our main aim isn’t just financial – we need to do it to reduce our carbon footprint, so that our energy usage doesn’t cost the Earth.
但我们的主要目的不只是省钱——我们这么做是为了减少碳足迹，让能源消耗不再以牺牲地球为代价。